{"data":[{"question":"Neither the students nor the teacher ___ to smoke in the classroom.","a":"allows","b":"is allowed","c":"allow","d":"have been allowed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When two or more singular nouns or pronouns are connected by or or nor, use a singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"When a person needs to take this medicine, ___ directions first.","a":"you will have to read","b":"you must to read","c":"you have to read","d":"he has to read","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A person- he","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"When we approached the campus, ___.","a":"we saw the tower","b":"one saw the tower","c":"the tower was seen","d":"we were seeing the tower","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In term of logic, answer \" we saw the tower\" is most suitable","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Collecting coins was his favorite pastime, but ___.","a":"he also enjoy music listening","b":"listening to music also gave him great pleasure","c":"also listening to music","d":"to listen to music was enjoyed by him also.","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \"collecting\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He did not sleep all night, and as happens to many and many a man who ___ the Bible, he understood for the first time the full meaning of the words read often before but passed by unnoticed.","a":"are reading","b":"have been reading","c":"reads","d":"have read","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Education is not only a preparation for later life; it is an aspect of life itself. The great bulk of the young now ____a minimum of twelve years in school; with kindergarten attendance becoming more widespread, more and more of the young will have spent thirteen to fifteen years attending school by the time they have finished high school.","a":"spend","b":"spends","c":"has spent","d":"has been spending","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" the great bulk\" which is uncountable noun and uses with singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Among the greatest discoveries of science not a few ___ by accident. Setting out to reach a certain goal, the investigator chances in his way upon a law, or an element, that had no place in his purpose. The discovery is a byproduct of his activity.","a":"have made","b":"have been made","c":"has made","d":"had made","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject - \"not a few (greatest discoveries)\"- is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Everything we shut our eyes to, everything we run away from, everything we deny or despise, ___ to defeat us in the end. What seems nasty, painful, evil, can become a source of beauty, joy and strength, if faced with open mind.","a":"serve","b":"serves","c":"are served","d":"have been serving","answer":"2","explain":"- We need a verb in active voice to make a completed sentence","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He wanted to make his son receive a good education, travel extensively, and ___.","a":"to other advantages are many more","b":"many other advantages","c":"enjoy many other advantages","d":"many other advantages are stored by him","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In the blank should be a verb which has the same form as \"travel\" and \"receive\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Everybody who ___ a fever must see a doctor immediately.","a":"is","b":"has","c":"are","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"-The pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them\n\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, anything someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs. Do not be misled by what follows of","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}